Guide to the Stewart Brand Papers M1237
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series IV: Projects
  - Metric debate: miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Metric debate: propaganda from government (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Metric debate: US Metric Board (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Metric debate: American National Metric Council and Metric Reporter (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Metric debate: history (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Metric debate: miscellaneous articles/newsclippings (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Metric debate: miscellaneous articles/newsclippings (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Metric debate: miscellaneous articles/newsclippings (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Metric debate: publications (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Metric debate: publications (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Metric debate: publications (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Metric debate: publications (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Metric debate: Federal Trade Commission Standards and Certification, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Metric debate: Getting a Better Understanding of the Metric System, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Metric debate: Metric Conversion Council, section 6.1, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Metric debate artifacts: t-shirts (2), flash cards, rulers (Box 44)
  - New Scientist miscellaneous, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - New Scientist miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - New Scientist miscellaneous, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Whole Earch Catalog miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Whole Earch Catalog miscellaneous, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Whole Earch television agreement, 1981-1982 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Management of Scarcity and Abundance: readings/resources, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Management of Scarcity and Abundance: benign genres, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Computer Conference Manual, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 1983 Computer Conference (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous conference notes, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - WESC [Whole Earth Software Conference], 1983 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - WESC [Whole Earth Software Conference], 1983 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - WESC [Whole Earth Software Conference], 1983 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Passkey Communications software, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Technological Progress and People, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Technological Progress and People, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Space Conference notes, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - WBSI [Western Behavioral Sciences Institute]: 1983 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - WBSI [Western Behavioral Sciences Institute]: printouts, [part 1], 1983 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - WBSI [Western Behavioral Sciences Institute]: printouts, [part 2], 1983 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - WBSI [Western Behavioral Sciences Institute]: printouts, [part 3], 1983 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - WBSI [Western Behavioral Sciences Institute]: 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - WBSI [Western Behavioral Sciences Institute]: 1984-1988 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - WBSI [Western Behavioral Sciences Institute]: 1989 Conference information (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - WBSI [Western Behavioral Sciences Institute]: participants/Alumni bio's (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - School of Management and Strategic Studies, 1987 bio's (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - WBSI membership directories, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Nova Scotia permits, 1972-1986 (with miscellaneous) (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Computer mailing lists, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Hacker's Conference, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Africa, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Sausalito, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Sausalito, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Sausalito, 1982-1984 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Sausalito, photographs (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Sausalito, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Sausalito Town Council, ca. 1984-1986 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Sausalito Town Council, ca. 1986-1987 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous property information, 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous property information (publications, conferences) 1983-1984 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous property information, 1984-1987 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous property information, 1985-1986 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Property photographs/slides, ca. 1975-1981 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - MIT, December 1985-March 1986 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: Vivarium (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: Vivarium (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: MIT (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: Around the Lab (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: Weisner Building (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: Negroponte (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: Human interface (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: movies, music, advanced TV, holography (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: Electronic publishing (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: Lab A.I., graphics, animation, speech (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: school, projects, A.I. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: computers (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: electronic mail, databases (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: miscellaneous newsclippings (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: satellite articles (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Media Lab research, 1986: media articles/newsclippings (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - "Benign Genres," 1983 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - "Brisk Office Desktop," ca. 1986 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - General Learning articles (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - How Businesses Learn, December 1985 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - General Learning: miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - General Learning: miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Learning Ideas, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Media Lab Book proposal and contract, 1986 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous articles, digitization (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Xerox PARC, computer advancements: 1985-1986 [interview with Steve Jobs] (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous articles, ca. 1986 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous articles (McLuhan) (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Neuman) (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous articles (Planet scale) (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous articles (technology) (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous articles (technology), 1985-1986 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - United Kingdom: receipts, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - United Kingdom: miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - United Kingdom: miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Varieties of Learning, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Media Lab: drafts, 1986-1987 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Media Lab: drafts, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Media Lab: drafts, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Media Lab: miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Media Lab: miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Media Lab: 1st draft [front matter - p.150] (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Media Lab: 1st draft [p. 151 - p.300] (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Media Lab: 1st draft [p. 301 - end] (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Media Lab: drafts, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Media Lab: drafts, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Media Lab, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Media Lab, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Media Lab: newsclippings, 1987-1988 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Media Lab: publications and correspondence, 1987 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Media Lab: publications and correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Media Lab: publications and correspondence, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Media Lab: publications and correspondence, 1988 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Media Lab: publications and correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Media Lab research index cards (Box 58)
  - Media Lab research index cards (Box 59)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Learning Conference, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1989 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Learning Conference: Tucson, Arizona, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Learning Conference: cv's, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Learning Conference: research material, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Learning Conference: budget and correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1992 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1992 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1992 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1992 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Learning Conference, 1986-1992 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Learning Conference/Media Lab: newsclippings, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Learning Conference #4: Big Sur, California, October 1988 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Learning Conference 1989: transcripts (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Learning Conference mailings: April 2, 1987-June 16, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Learning Conference mailings: July 2, 1987-September 9, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Learning Conference mailings: October 1, 1987-April 16, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Learning Conference mailings: May 4, 1988-September 12, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Learning Conference, 1989 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Learning Conference, 1987-1989 [Costa Rica photographs] (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - GBN [Global Business Network], 1988-1989: Worldview service (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft), 1988 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft), 1988 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft), 1988 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft), 1988 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft), 1988 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft), 1988 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft), 1988 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft, notes, etc.) (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book (draft, notes, etc.) (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - The 1989 GBN Scenario Book: newsclippings, articles (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Talks/conferences, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Talks/conferences, 1988-1992 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Talks/conferences, 1988-1992 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Talks/conferences, 1988-1992 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Talks/conferences, 1988-1992 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Whole Earth, WELL, POINT: 1989-1993 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Whole Earth, WELL, POINT: 1989-1993 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Whole Earth, WELL, POINT: 1989-1993 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Whole Earth, WELL, POINT: 1989-1993 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Whole Earth, WELL, POINT: 1989-1993 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Santa Fe Institute, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Santa Fe Institute, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Santa Fe Institute, 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Santa Fe Institute, 1991-1993 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Santa Fe Institute, 1992-1997 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - GBN book club, 1988-1989 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - GBN book club, 1988-1991 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - GBN book club, 1992-1994 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - GBN book club, 1995-1997 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - GBN book club, 1998-2000 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - GBN book club, miscellaneous (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - GBN: Delancey Street/Mime Silbert, ca. 1990 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1991-1993 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1991-1993 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1991-1994 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - GBN, 1993-1996 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1993-1996 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1993-1996 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1993-1996 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1993-1996 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1994 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1994-1996 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - GBN, 1994-1996 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - GBN, 1994-1996 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1994-1996 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1994-1996 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1995-1996 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1995-1996 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - GBN, 1995-1996 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - GBN, 1995-1996 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1995-1996 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1995-1998 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1995-1998 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1995-1998 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - GBN, 1997-2000 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - GBN miscellaneous, 1997-2000 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Talks, 1997 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Talks, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Talks, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Talks, 1997 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Clock of the Long Now (draft), ca. 1998 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Clock of the Long Now (draft), ca. 1998 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Clock of the Long Now (draft), ca. 1998 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Clock of the Long Now: miscellaneous, 1999-2000 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Clock of the Long Now: published edition, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Clock of the Long Now: research index cards (Box 92)
  - Clock of the Long Now: research index cards (Box 93)
  - How Buildings Learn: Carrol House, Maryland (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: Fernau and Hartman (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: John Abrams (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: "random" (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: William Rawn Associates (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: Chris Wilson (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - How Buildings Learn: Montpelier (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - How Buildings Learn: M.I.T. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - How Buildings Learn: Duany Plater-Zyberk (DPZ) (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - How Buildings Learn: Paul Groth (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - How Buildings Learn: short interviews (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - How Buildings Learn: Whole Earth book orders (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - How Buildings Learn: Dorsey Mansion, New Mexico (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - How Buildings Learn: Jonathon Rose (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - How Buildings Learn: DEGW (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - How Buildings Learn: DEGW (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - How Buildings Learn: Chatsworth (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - How Buildings Learn: CRSS (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: David Sellers (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: California Historical Society (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: Ellen Manchester (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: Tor House (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: Mount Vernon (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - How Buildings Learn: McDonald's House (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - How Buildings Learn: Zuni (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - How Buildings Learn: Turkey (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - How Buildings Learn: Seitz House (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - How Buildings Learn: Bldg. 20 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - How Buildings Learn: cover, by Brantley (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - How Buildings Learn: Lewis Thomas Building (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - How Buildings Learn: acknowledgement and publicity (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - How Buildings Learn: free copies (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - How Buildings Learn: photo permissions (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - How Buildings Learn: National Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: financial (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: retired photographic requests (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: prior text (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: scenarios for buildings (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: scenarios for buildings (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - How Buildings Learn: Richard Rogers (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - How Buildings Learn: Richard Rogers (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous, 1990-1993 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1994 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1995 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous correspondence regarding British shoot (film/documentary), 1997 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: American shoot (film/documentary), ca. 1997 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: miscellaneous articles/brochures (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - How Buildings Learn: photographs (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - How Buildings Learn: published paperback edition, 1994 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - How Buildings Learn: published hardback edition, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - How Buildings Learn: Berkeley class, photographs, ca. 1988 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - How Buildings Learn: Berkeley class materials, 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - How Buildings Learn: Berkeley class materials, 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - How Buildings Learn: Berkeley class notes, 1987-1988 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - How Buildings Learn: related publications (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - How Buildings Learn: research index cards (Box 103)
  - How Buildings Learn: research index cards (Box 104)
  - How Buildings Learn: research index cards (Box 105)
  - How Buildings Learn: research index cards (Box 106)
  - How Buildings Learn: scrapbook (Box 107)
- Series V: Miscellaneous
  The large majority of this series consists of various articles, publications, and newspaper clippings that have reference to Stewart Brand and his different projects. Also included are Brand's articles and personal work regarding earthquakes, in particular the 1989 San Francisco earthquake.
  - Miscellaneous: "The San Francisco Earthquake," by Vincent McHugh, 1960 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous: "Proceedings of NITINOL Hear Engine Conference," September 1978 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous: Rose Moss stories, 1978-1986 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous: E. I. Couse exhibition on The American Indian, 1980 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous: "L'Essor de la Premier Cybernetique," Jean-Pierre Dupuy, ca. 1986 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous: Accelerated Learning Hypothesis, 1986 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous: "Economics and Security in East/West Relations," Heinrich Vogel, 1988 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Earthquake reference material, 1989-1990 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Earthquake reference material, 1989-1990 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - San Francisco earthquake photographs, 1989 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - "Toward a Theory of Woodstock Nation," Rachile Barrett Martin, 1996 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Oversize: Ken Kesey articles, ca. 1966 (Box 109, Folder 1)